- void enqueue (int n) // append n to the queue 
- int dequeue () // remove the first item in the queue, and return its value 
- int first() // get the first item without removing it first 
- int last () // get the last item without removing it 
- void clear () // clear (initialise) the queue 
- bool IsEmpty () // returns true if the queue is empty 
- bool IsFull () // returns true if the queue is full
 - void print () // print the entire queue 
- int position (int n) // returns the position of n in the queue, or -1 if n is not in the queue 
- void remove (int n) // remove n from the queue

